# PEDRO MEDINA ROBLES

COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEER

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE: 13260429

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

PHP (OOP)
Composer
MySQL
MariaDB
jSON
GIT
UML
HTML5, JS

CSS3 AVANZADO AJAX jQuery

WebApps (Angular)
Bootstrap

Windows Server, Linux Server

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative
Organized
Results oriented
Tenacious
Patient

#### CONTACT

9371678906
pedro.medina.ro97@outlook.com
Col. Tascoob Street River Mezcalapa
Block 3 #8
CP.86500, H.Cárdenas, Tabasco
GitHub; PedroMedina97
Web: https://pedromedina97.github.io/

#### OTHER ABILITIES

TECHNICAL SUPPORT FOR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT
-NETWORKS
-SERVERS
-MICROSOFT OFFICE COMPLETE
-PHOTOSHOP, ILLUSTRATOR, PREMIERE PRO (BASIC)

#### **IDIOMAS**

English B2 conversational

### COURSES | TRAININGS BOOTSTRAP

**UDEMY** 

PHP

ODEMY

JAVASCRIPT, NODE JS, ANGULAR, JQUERY

UDEMY

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a Computer Systems Engineer graduated from the Universidad del Valle de Mexico, I have worked on projects in the corporate sector, oil, automotive, agricultural and recently administrative accounting integrating map technologies, REDUX patterns, Angular, PHP, Node.js so my skills are of a Full Stack Developer, but I can perform without problems as Back End or Front End.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### **PROFESSIONAL CONSULTANT SERVICES**

NTTDATA - CITI | JULY. 2024 - OCTOBER. 2024 (PARTIAL)

FIGMA-based Template Development
API web services consumption
Development of re-usable components in ANGULAR
Bootstrap
KANBAN, DevOps, Agile, SCRUM

#### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

KOUD | August. 2023 - August. 2024

FIGMA-based Template Development
API web services consumption
Development of re-usable components in ANGULAR
REDUX
CSS and SCSS animation development
Maps (Leaflet)
Bootstrap, Materialize
KANBAN, DevOps, Agile, SCRUM

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEERING ASSISTANT**

IPS GROUP | FEBRUARY, 2022 - MARCH, 2023

Development and consumption of REST API services (PHP)
Library integration (Composer)
Databases (MySQL, MariaDB)
Front-End Development (Angular, jQuery)
Technical support to internal and remote users
Process improvement
Planning with Microsoft Project, SCRUM, Jira Software

#### PROJECT LEADER / JUNIOR PROGRAMMER

Xinergia Group | NOVIEMBRE 2019 - ENERO. 2022

Overall project management using agile methodologies (SCRUM) Project and deliverables planning with Microsoft Project Dashboard management Analyzing and documenting information from client minutes Use of digital communication and file transfer tools Relational database modeling Design of process, flow and UML diagrams Web design (Angular Framework, Bootstrap) API's development and integration

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **COMPUTER SYSTEMS ENGINEERING**

Universidad del Valle de México | 2016 - 2021